Guide to the Glenway Wescott Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1900-89, n.d.; Series I; 53.76; (129 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - GW and MW to Szold-Fritz, Bernardine, 1927-77, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 1594-1605)
      BSF and various enclosures removed
      from original correspondence: one
      photograph, receipts, and
      manuscript: "Sequel for Lin Yu Tang"
      by BSF (n.d.)
    - Szold, J., 1928 Apr 22 (Box 105, Folder 1606)
    - "S" general, 1927-91, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 1607-1610)
    - "S" general, 1927-91, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1611-1612)
    - Tambimuttu, 1965 Jul 25 (Box 106, Folder 1613)
    - Tanner, Allen, 1945-70 (Box 106, Folder 1614)
    - Tate, Allen, 1940-72 (Box 106, Folder 1615)
    - Tawney, Lenore, 1969-75 (Box 106, Folder 1616)
      to Barbara Wescott & GW
    - Taylor, Henry, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 1617)
    - Taylor, Rachel Annard, 1932 Mar 17 (Box 106, Folder 1618)
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel, 1932-57, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1619-1622)
      to MW, GW, & GPL; includes
      letter from PT to Russell Lynes
      & Mildred Akin
    - GW and MW to Tchelitchew, Pavel, 1932-54 (Box 106, Folder 1623)
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1624)
      letter of introduction for MW to
      Edith and Osbert Sitwell
    - Tennant, Stephen, 1974 Mar (Box 106, Folder 1625)
    - Terzian, Manug; Terzian, Michael, 1971-75 (Box 106, Folder 1626)
    - Thayer, Jeanne, 1987-88 (Box 106, Folder 1627)
    - Thompson, Russell, 1943, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 1628)
    - Thomson, Virgil, 1938-81, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1629)
    - Thurber, James, 1936-37, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1630)
    - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1950 Jan 17 (Box 106, Folder 1631)
    - Tobey, Mark, 1962 Feb 6 (Box 107, Folder 1632)
    - Toklas, Alice, 1952, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 1633)
    - Tone, Aileen, 1947-68, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1634)
    - Toogood, Granville, 1938 (Box 107, Folder 1635)
    - Tooker, George, 1947-78, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1636)
    - Trebay, Guy, 1975 Oct 12 (Box 107, Folder 1637)
    - Tree, Mona, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1638)
      See also: Mona Richards, Box 94, folder 1403
    - Truslow, Marguerite, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 1639)
    - Tunley, Roul, 1961-77 (Box 107, Folder 1640)
    - Turbyfill, Mark, 1948-66 (Box 107, Folder 1641)
    - Turnbull, Andrew, 1958-62 (Box 107, Folder 1642)
    - Tyler, Parker, 1956-66, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1643)
    - Tyng, Lila, 1965, 1978, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1644)
    - "T" general, 1945-88, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1645-1646)
    - Udall, Stewart, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1647)
    - Union College, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1648)
    - U.S. National Commission for UNESCO, 1950-53 (Box 107, Folder 1649)
    - United States. Office of the President, 1943, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 1650)
    - University of Chicago, 1919-78, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1651)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1652)
    - University of Maryland, 1967-75 (Box 107, Folder 1653)
    - University of Texas, 1973-83 (Box 107, Folder 1654)
    - University of Utah Writer's Conference, 1956-70 (Box 107, Folder 1655)
    - University of Virginia, 1962-63 (Box 107, Folder 1656)
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1962-81 (Box 107, Folder 1657)
    - Unna, Sarah, 1920 Mar 8 (Box 107, Folder 1658)
      to GW & Arthur Yvor Winters
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1962 Sep 5 (Box 107, Folder 1659)
    - Updike, John, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1660)
    - U.S. Camera magazine, 1938 (Box 107, Folder 1661)
    - "U" general, 1949-83 (Box 107, Folder 1662)
    - Van Arsdale, William K., 1937-88, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1663)
    - Vandercook, John W., 1945 Mar 30 (Box 108, Folder 1664)
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1949-71 (Box 108, Folder 1665)
    - Van Gent, Cock, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1666)
    - Van Krimpen, Jan, 1930-59, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1667-1669)
      to MW & Barbara Harrison
      (Wescott); includes letters from
      MW
    - Van Rensselaer, Schuyler, Mrs., 1932-35, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1670)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1940-56 (Box 108, Folder 1671)
    - Van Veen, Felicia, 1970-73, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1672)
    - Venturi, Lionello, 1950 Jan 31 (Box 108, Folder 1673)
    - Verity, Dennis H., 1968, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 1674)
    - Viking Press, 1949-74 (Box 108, Folder 1675)
    - Villon, Jacques, 1955 (Box 108, Folder 1676)
    - Von Auw, Ivan, 1967-74 (Box 108, Folder 1677)
    - Von Ihering, George-Albrecht, 1926-72, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1678)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 1679)
    - Vreeland, Diana, 1950-73, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1680)
    - "V" general, 1927-86, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1681)
    - W. Colston Leigh, Inc., 1945, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 1682)
    - W., G. D., 1935, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1683)
    - Wade, Frederick, 1938 Nov 18 (Box 108, Folder 1684)
    - Wald, Max, 1944-45, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1685)
    - Walker, Herschel Carey, 1950-66, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1686)
    - Walker, Jeff, 1961-64 (Box 108, Folder 1687)
    - Warburton, Samuel, 1973-81, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1688)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1940-81 (Box 108, Folder 1689)
    - Wasserman, Burton, 1969-82 (Box 109, Folder 1690)
      to GW & Lloyd Wescott
    - Watkins, Franklin, 1948 Apr 17 (Box 109, Folder 1691)
    - Watson, Hildegarde, 1962, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 1692)
    - Watson, Steven, 1986-87 (Box 109, Folder 1693)
    - Waugh, Evelyn, 1954 Jul 5 (Box 109, Folder 1694)
    - Weil, Hope, 1930-78, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1695)
    - Weiss, Theodore, 1951-55 (Box 109, Folder 1696)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1945, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 1697)
    - Wesely, Donald, 1945-46 (Box 109, Folder 1698)
    - West, John J., 1959 (Box 109, Folder 1699)
      & letter from Mildred Rudd to GW
    - West, Rebecca, 1930, 1974, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1700)
    - White, E. B., 1960-71 (Box 109, Folder 1701)
    - White, Katharine, 1965-66 (Box 109, Folder 1702)
    - Whitmore, George, 1974 Jul 22 (Box 109, Folder 1703)
    - Whitney, Betsey, 1949, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1704)
    - "Who's Who" publications, 1968-78, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1705)
    - Widdecombe, John, 1946-67, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1706)
    - Wiemeler, Ignatz, 1936-51, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1707)
    - Wilder, Isabel, 1945-82 (Box 109, Folder 1708)
      to IW from Dalma Brunauer, letter
      from A. Wilder to Dalma Brunauer,
      letter from Amos Wilder to Dalma
      Brunauer
    - GW to Wilder, Isabel, 1957-77 (Box 109, Folder 1709)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1928-73, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1710-1712)
    - GW and MW to Wilder, Thornton, 1937-73 (Box 110, Folder 1713-1714)
    - Wille, Frederick G., 1945-83 (Box 110, Folder 1715)
    - William Morris Agency, 1944-77 (Box 110, Folder 1716-1718)
      to GW; icludes letter from GW
      includes letter from Walter Bradbury
      to Jane Wilson
    - Williams, Tennessee, 1953, 1974, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1719)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1923 (Box 110, Folder 1720)
    - Willis, Patricia, 1979-80 (Box 110, Folder 1721)
    - Wilson, Edmund; Wilson, Elena, 1941-75 (Box 110, Folder 1722)
    - Wilson, Hugh, 1952-62 (Box 110, Folder 1723)
    - Wilson, Robert, 1976-81, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1724)
    - Wimmer, Kurt, 1926-1959 (Box 110, Folder 1725)
    - Wind, Edgar; Wind, Margaret, 1941-56, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1726)
    - Windham, Donald, 1945-81, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1727)
    - Winsor, Kathleen, 1945 Mar 22 (Box 110, Folder 1728)
    - Winters, Harry L., 1920 Jul 9 (Box 110, Folder 1729)
    - Winters, Janet Lewis, 1919-87, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1730-1732)
    - GW and MW to Winters, Janet Lewis, 1982, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1733)
    - Winters, Yvor, 1919-62 (Box 111, Folder 1734-1735)
      to Mrs. Bruce Wescott and
      Elizabeth Wescott
    - Winthrop, Emmeline, 1939-47, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1736)
    - Wojtasik, Ted, 1981-87 (Box 111, Folder 1737)
    - Wolff, Eleanor, 1978, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 1738)
    - Wolff, Kurt, 1944 Mar 24 (Box 111, Folder 1739)
    - Wolfson, Victor, 1945 (Box 111, Folder 1740)
    - Woody, Jack, 1980-81 (Box 111, Folder 1741)
    - Woolmer, J. Howard, 1974-75 (Box 111, Folder 1742)
    - Wright, Richard, 1945 Jan 3 (Box 111, Folder 1743)
    - Wrightsman, Jayne, 1965-69, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1744)
    - "W" general, 1940-83, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1745-1749)
    - Xavier Fourcade, Inc., 1986 (Box 112, Folder 1750)
      to [MW?]
    - Yates, Peter, 1962 Jul 27 (Box 112, Folder 1751)
    - Yeon, John, 1933-72, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1752-1756)
    - Yoken, Melvin, 1968-74 (Box 112, Folder 1757)
    - Yow, Alexander Jensen, 1963-81, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1758)
    - Yudelowitz, Jacqueline, 1979-82, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1759)
    - Yuize, Shinichi, 1955-65 (Box 112, Folder 1760)
    - Yurka, Blanche, 1970 Jun 1 (Box 112, Folder 1761)
    - "Y" general, 1955-76 (Box 112, Folder 1762)
    - Zaoussailoff, Alexandra ["Choura"], 1963-72 (Box 112, Folder 1763)
    - Zayas, Marius de, 1948 Apr 12 (Box 112, Folder 1764)
    - Zich, Adell, 1962-87 (Box 112, Folder 1765)
    - "Z" general, 1934-87 (Box 112, Folder 1766)
    - Unidentified
      - "Anne" to MW, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1767)
      - "Beth", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1768)
      - "David", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1769)
      - "Emmy", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1770)
      - "Frances", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1771)
      - "Francis" to MW, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1772)
      - "Jack", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1773)
      - "Julian", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1774)
      - "Kay" to MW, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1775)
      - "Kipper", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1776)
      - "M?, Land" (Box 113, Folder 1777)
      - "Min", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1778)
      - "Newbold", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1779)
      - "Peter", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1780)
      - "Philip" [Servant], 1946 Jan 21 (Box 113, Folder 1781)
      - "Ralph", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1782)
      - "Rick", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1783)
      - "Ted", n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1784)
      - "The Old Friends" (Box 113, Folder 1785)
      - Unidentified, ca. 1932, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1786-1789)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1790)
      - Unidentified to MW, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1791)
      - Unidentified Envelopes, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1792)
      - Unidentified from GW, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 1793-1795)
      - Unidentified from MW, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 1796)
    - Condolence and "get well" letters to MW, 1987, n.d. (Box 116, Folder 1797-1798)
    - Christmas card scrapbook, 1934-45 (Box 117, Folder 1799)
      [Includes cards from: Paul Cadmus,
      Moore Crossthwaite, and Agnes
      [Rindge?]
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, 1946-59 (Box 117a, Folder 1800-1806)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, 1960-64 (Box 118, Folder 1807-1817)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, 1965-67 (Box 119, Folder 1818-1827)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, 1968-75 (Box 120, Folder 1828-1839)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, 1976-88, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1840-1852)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1853-1863)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1864-1873)
    - Christmas cards to GW & MW, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 1874-1881)
  - THIRD-PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - "Angus" to Lansdale, Nelson, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1882)
    - Ashby, Ivan to Connolly, John Robert, 1968, 1971, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1883)
    - "Bambi" to Aguilar, Mauricio, 1945 Oct 19 (Box 125, Folder 1884)
    - Bauduin, Armand to Viviano, Catherine, 1973 Nov 20 (Box 125, Folder 1885)
      [copy]
    - Butler, Earl to "George", n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1886)
    - Bynner, Witter to Johnson, Spud, 1923 Dec 21 (Box 125, Folder 1887)
      [copy, annotated]
    - Bynner, Witter to Purnell, Ida, 1926 Nov 10 (Box 125, Folder 1888)
    - [Cadmus?], Paul to Miller, Christian William, 1970 Mar 16 (Box 125, Folder 1889)
    - Cagle, William R. to Wilson, Robert A., 1979 Feb 13 (Box 125, Folder 1890)
    - Capote, Truman to Kirstein, Lincoln, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1891)
      [with note from "Henri"
      [Cartier-Bresson?]]
    - Carstairs, Joe to Lynes, George Platt, [1942 Mar 27] (Box 125, Folder 1892)
    - Chandlee, William H. to Connolly, John R., 1952-53 (Box 125, Folder 1893)
    - Chang, C.L. to Fritz, [Chester?], 1929 Jul 3 (Box 125, Folder 1894)
    - Connolly, John Robert to Unidentified, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1895)
    - "Cressida" and "Adam" to Raymond Mortimer, 1961 May 24 (Box 125, Folder 1895a)
    - DeLamar, Alice to [Kirstein], Lincoln, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1896)
    - "Dorothy" to Wescott, Lloyd, 1979 Sep 24 (Box 125, Folder 1897)
    - Gebhard, Paul to Zaoussailoff, Alexandra, 1963 Nov 15 (Box 125, Folder 1898)
    - Gerder & Co. to Maugham, W. Somerset, 1952 Jun 10 (Box 125, Folder 1899)
    - Gillett, William to Beecher, Leonard T., 1900 Dec 13 (Box 125, Folder 1900)
    - Goldbeck, Eva to Wescott, Elizabeth, 1920 Jan 3 (Box 125, Folder 1901)
    - Gordon, Robert, Rev to Wescott, Bruce P., Mr. and Mrs., 1926 Mar 13 (Box 125, Folder 1902)
    - Halpern, Irving W. to Mahan, Edna, 1947 May 6 (Box 125, Folder 1903)
    - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. to Hagen, Beulah, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1904)
    - [Harrison?], Francis to Wescott, Barbara, 1933 [Feb 3?] (Box 125, Folder 1905)
    - [Hirth], Fred to [Butler], Earl, 1977, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1906)
    - Hopkins, Harry L. to Wescott, Barbara, 1945 Dec 12 (Box 125, Folder 1907)
    - Humphrey, William to Wescott, Barbara, 1967 Jan 1 (Box 125, Folder 1908)
    - Inge, William to Miller, Christian William, 1958 Mar 11 (Box 125, Folder 1909)
    - Jack, Homer Randolph to Porter (Box 125, Folder 1910)
    - Katherine Anne
    - Jacob, May to Manoli, Mitchell, 1943 Feb 20 (Box 125, Folder 1911)
    - Jayakar, Mrs. to Crishna, Mrs. Amie, 1945 Apr 17 (Box 125, Folder 1912)
    - Keppel, Charles T. to d'Harnoncourt, Réné, 1953 May 26 (Box 125, Folder 1913)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln to Lynes, George Platt, 1946-55, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1914)
    - Knollys, Eardley to "Marie", n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1915)
    - Laurents, Arthur to Miller, Christian William, 1957, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1916)
    - Lansdale, Nelson to Cadmus, Paul, 1942 Sep 26 (Box 125, Folder 1917)
    - "Leah" to Wescott, Lloyd, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1918)
    - Lebeck, Michael to Phelps, Robert, 1967 Jul 31 (Box 125, Folder 1919)
    - Lee, Arthur to Ogden, Paul, 1930 Nov 22 (Box 125, Folder 1920)
    - Lewis, Sinclair to MacVeagh, Lincoln, 1924 Nov 12 (Box 125, Folder 1921)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques to "Mademoiselle, 1944 Jul 14 (Box 125, Folder 1922)
    - Miller"
    - Loeb, Mindret to Namara, Marguerite, [ca. 1925] (Box 125, Folder 1923)
    - Loovis, Dick to "Robert", 1975 Sep 15 (Box 125, Folder 1924)
    - Luchs, Alison to Wescott, Lloyd, 1986 Jan 31 (Box 125, Folder 1925)
    - Lynes, Adelaide to Porter, Katherine Anne, [ca. 1956] (Box 125, Folder 1926)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Howard, Chuck, 1951 May 17 (Box 125, Folder 1927)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Lynes, Joseph, 1929 Feb 26 (Box 125, Folder 1928)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Lynes, Russell, 1947 Mar 27 (Box 125, Folder 1929)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Miller, Christian William, Jr., 1945-46 (Box 125, Folder 1930)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Steward, Samuel M., 1953 Nov 19 (Box 125, Folder 1931)
    - Lynes, George Platt to "Mr. Street", n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1932)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Szold-Fritz, Bernardine, 1927-50, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1933)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Wescott, Bruce, ca. 1933 (Box 125, Folder 1934)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Wescott, Barbara, 1932-55, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1935)
    - Lynes, George Platt to Wheeler, Fred Monroe, 1930 Oct (Box 125, Folder 1936)
    - Lynes, Joseph to Lynes, George Platt, 1930 Aug 19 (Box 125, Folder 1937)
    - Lynes, Russell to Lynes, George Platt, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1938)
    - MacGregor, Frank S. to Miller, Christian William, 1945 Feb 6 (Box 125, Folder 1939)
    - Malouf, Carl A. to "Fred and Paul" (Box 125, Folder 1940)
    - Moody, Mrs. William Vaughn to Wescott, Josephine, 1922 Jan 5 (Box 125, Folder 1941)
    - Moore, D. Langley, Mrs. to Mr. Sackville-West, 1961 Jul 28 (Box 125, Folder 1942)
    - Moore, Marianne to Mr. Bryan, 1957 Aug 23 (Box 125, Folder 1942a)
    - Moore, Marianne to Bubley, Esther, ca. 1957 Apr (Box 125, Folder 1942b)
      [transcription]
    - Moore, Marianne to Cantwell, Robert, 1951 Dec 21 (Box 125, Folder 1942c)
    - Moore, Marianne to Connolly, John, 1964 Mar 27 (Box 125, Folder 1943)
    - Moore, Marianne to Lynes, George Platt, 1950 Nov 2 (Box 125, Folder 1944)
    - Moore, Marianne to Miller, William, 1958 Aug 26 (Box 125, Folder 1945)
      [Includes proof copy of "The
      Arctic Ox"]
    - Moore, Marianne to Wescott, Barbara, 1950-58 (Box 125, Folder 1946)
    - Mortimer, Raymond to Curtiss, Mina, 1948 Aug 22 (Box 125, Folder 1947)
    - Mortimer, Raymond to Maugham, W. Somerset, 1948 Jul 11 (Box 125, Folder 1948)
    - Mortimer, Raymond to Moore, Marianne, 1967 Nov 14 (Box 125, Folder 1948a)
    - Norris, Kathleen to Wescott, Barbara, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 1949)
    - O'Hara, John to O'Hara, William, 1961 Feb 9 (Box 125, Folder 1950)
    - O'Higgins, Patrick to Lynes, George Platt, 1947 Mar 10 (Box 125, Folder 1951)
    - Parrish, Anne to Wescott, [Barbara], 1954 Apr 30 (Box 125, Folder 1952)
    - Peck, Mrs. to Wescott, Josephine, 1934 Mar 30 (Box 126, Folder 1953)
    - Perlin, Bernard to Rothschild, Pauline de, 1948 Aug 31 (Box 126, Folder 1954)
    - Perlin, Bernard to Wescott, Barbara, 1971, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1955)
    - Perret, Pierre to Faith, Robert, 1957 Aug 6 (Box 126, Folder 1956)
    - Phelps, Robert to Ashby, Ivan, 1968 Jul 10 (Box 126, Folder 1957)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph to Miller, Christian William, 1958 Aug 30 (Box 126, Folder 1958)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Erskine, Albert, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1959)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Hagen, Beulah, 1949 Aug 22 (Box 126, Folder 1960)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Lynes, George Platt, 1955, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1961)
      [copies]
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Lynes, Russell, [1947] (Box 126, Folder 1962)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Moore, Marianne, 1968 Jun 16 (Box 126, Folder 1963)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne to Wescott, Barbara, Lloyd and Deborah, 1935-59, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1964)
    - Ross, Isabel to Herdman, Ramona, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1965)
    - Sergeant, Elizabeth Shepley to Lawrence, Elizabeth, 1962 Oct 9 (Box 126, Folder 1966)
    - Szold-Fritz, Bernardine to Fritz, Chester, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1967)
    - Szold-Fritz, Bernardine to Wescott, Barbara, ca. 1929-50, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1968-1972)
      Includes letters from BSF to "Frances"
      and "Madame Chesaux"
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel to Wescott, Barbara, 1933-57, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1973)
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel to Lynes, George Platt, 1936 Jun 25 (Box 126, Folder 1974)
    - Travis, David to Yow, Alexander Jensen, 1976 Sep 30 (Box 126, Folder 1975)
    - Wescott, Barbara to Harrison, Maria Teresa, 1959 Jun 7 (Box 126, Folder 1976)
    - Wescott, Barbara to "Mrs. Hughes", n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1977)
    - Wescott, Barbara to Porter, Katherine Anne, 1934 Nov 12 (Box 126, Folder 1978)
    - Wescott, Barbara to Miller, Christian William, 1944, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 1979)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Bernhard, Edmund, 1980 Jul 21 (Box 126, Folder 1980)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Ivry, Benjamin, 1982 May 25 (Box 126, Folder 1981)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Pathé News, Inc., 1938 Feb 28 (Box 126, Folder 1982)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Seaton, R. Kirk, 1978 Dec 28 (Box 126, Folder 1983)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Time magazine, 1964 Dec 21 (Box 126, Folder 1984)
    - Wescott, Lloyd to Warburton, Samuel, 1979 Jan 2 (Box 126, Folder 1985)
    - Wheeler, Fred Monroe to "Mr. Kinne", 1940 Apr 30 (Box 126, Folder 1986)
    - Wilder, Thornton to Canfield, Cass, 1967 Jul 28 (Box 126, Folder 1987)
    - Wilkins, Bill to Wescott, Barbara, 1967 Jan 21 (Box 126, Folder 1988)
    - Zayas, Marius and Virginia to Wescott, Barbara and Szold-Fritz, Bernardine, 1925-39, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1989)
    - Letter of recommendation for Stevenson, John from Bernstein, Sydney, 1976 Mar 20 (Box 126, Folder 1990)
    - Letters of congratulation to Bruce Wescott re: GW, 1927, 1932, nd (Box 126, Folder 1991)
    - Letters of recommendation/introduction for MW, 1921-62, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1992)
    - Used postcards [collected by MW?], n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1993)
    - Unidentified 3rd party correspondence (Box 126, Folder 1994)
- Journals and Notebooks, 1920s-1980s; Series II; 54.18; (129 boxes)
  Series II, Journals and Notebooks,
  consists of three subseries: Journals and
  Notebooks are arranged chronologically
  Journal Excerpts are arranged by title.
  - JOURNALS
    - Loose pages, 1920s (Box 127, Folder 1995)
    - Journal binder: "Chronology of the 30s", 1937 Jan-Feb (Box 127, Folder 1996)
    - Journal binder, 1937 Jun-Dec (Box 127, Folder 1997)
    - Journal binder, 1937 Jul-Dec (Box 128, Folder 1998)
    - Loose pages, 1937-38 (Box 128, Folder 1999)
    - Journal binder, 1937-38 (Box 128, Folder 2000)
    - Journal binder, 1938 Jan-Dec (Box 129, Folder 2001)
    - Loose pages: "European Diary", 1938 Mar-Apr (Box 129, Folder 2002-2003)
    - Loose pages, 1938 Mar-Apr (Box 129, Folder 2004)
    - Journal binder, 1938 Apr-Aug (Box 130, Folder 2005)
    - Loose pages, 1938 Apr-Dec (Box 130, Folder 2006)
    - Journal binder, 1939 Jan-Dec (Box 130, Folder 2007)
    - Loose pages: "Awake in Darkness, Asleep in Light", 1939 Jan-Dec (Box 130, Folder 2008)
    - Material pulled from journals for "Continual Lessons", 1937-39 (Box 131, Folder 2009)
    - Loose pages, 1930s (Box 131, Folder 2010-2013)
    - Journal binders, 1940 Jan-Dec (Box 132, Folder 2014-2015)
    - Journal binder, 1941 Jan-Dec (Box 132, Folder 2016)
    - Journal binder, 1941-44 (Box 133, Folder 2017)
    - Journal binder, 1942 (Box 133, Folder 2018)
    - Journal binder, 1943 Jan-Jul, 1944 Feb (Box 134, Folder 2019)
    - Journal binder, 1943-44 (Box 134, Folder 2020)
      Includes: folder of loose pages
    - Journal binder, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 2021)
    - Journal binder, 1945 Jan-Sep (Box 135, Folder 2022)
    - Journal binder, 1945 Jan-Jul (Box 136, Folder 2023)
    - Journal binder, 1945 Aug-Nov (Box 136, Folder 2024)
    - Journal binder, 1945 May-1946 Aug (Box 137, Folder 2025)
    - Journal binder, 1945 Oct-1946 Mar (Box 137, Folder 2026)
    - Journal binder, 1947 Jan-Mar (Box 138, Folder 2027)
    - Journal binder, 1947 Jan-Jun (Box 138, Folder 2028)
    - Journal binder: "1947 Material in Green Box Texts", 1947 Jan-Jul (Box 139, Folder 2029)
    - Journal binder, 1947 Jun-Dec (Box 139, Folder 2030)
    - Journal binder: "The Damage & Other Pieces", 1947 (Box 140, Folder 2031)
    - Journal binder, 1947 Jul-1948 Oct (Box 140, Folder 2032)
    - Journal binder, 1948 Jan-Apr (Box 140, Folder 2033)
    - Journal binder, 1948 May-Aug (Box 141, Folder 2034)
    - Journal binder, 1948 Sep-Dec (Box 141, Folder 2035)
    - Journal binder, 1948 Nov-Dec (Box 142, Folder 2036)
    - Journal binder, [1948] (Box 142, Folder 2037)
    - Journal binder, 1948 Nov-1949 Feb (Box 143, Folder 2038)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Jan-Mar (Box 143, Folder 2039)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Jan-Mar (Box 144, Folder 2040)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Mar-Apr (Box 144, Folder 2041)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Apr-May (Box 145, Folder 2042)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Apr-Jun (Box 145, Folder 2043)
    - Journal binder, 1949 May-Sep (Box 146, Folder 2044)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Jun (Box 146, Folder 2045)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Jul-Aug (Box 147, Folder 2046)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Aug-Sep (Box 147, Folder 2047)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Sep-Nov (Box 148, Folder 2048)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Oct-Dec (Box 148, Folder 2049)
    - Journal binder, 1949 Nov-Dec (Box 149, Folder 2050)
    - Material pulled from journals for "Continual Lessons", 1940-46 (Box 149, Folder 2051-2058)